# Ryo Lambert

# Web Dev / Front-End Engineer / Designer

Albuquerque, NM



## Skills.

UI / UX Design Graphic Design / Animation SEO / Analytics Project Management

Branding / Social Media

IT Network Triage SEO / Analytics

Community Outreach / Engagement

Adobe CC Suite

# Languages

HTML CSS .lava PHP MvS0L

# Frameworks

#### Front-End:

P5.js / three.js / particles.js Aiax / iOuerv / fontawesome

## Libraries / Tech

## Front-End:

Bootstrap / Materialize / Angular JS

## Back-End:

T.AMP

# Design Work



instagram.com/relevant\_design/



codepen.io/Relevant\_Design/

# Sites

nmsk.org

eat-mogumogu.com

# **Objective**

It's my mission and passion to utilize today's technologies in only the most visually captivating, creative, and interactive mediums possible to give your company's hard work and great ideas the market and profits it deserves. I love bringing a scientific approach to web development, iterating upon the fundamentals of human cognition, emotion, and behavior to create digital experiences people enjoy coming back to again and again. I excel in fast-paced environments, working with teams, creative design/problem-solving, and learning on the go. Let's collaborate and build something!

## **Experience**

### Fullstack Web Developer Intern, Deep Dive Coding

Worked with developing both the front and back end of personal and group capstone projects using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JS, jQuery, MySQL, and PHP 7. Integration with RESTful APIs such as Google Maps, Places, and Recreation.gov.

# Web / Graphic Designer, Freelance

Jan 2016 - Present

Developed sites personalized for client needs. Created graphics/branding/mobile design for sites, alongside social media campaign development with included copy writing and content creation. And streamlined/integrated SEO and Google Analytics into sites for optimal exposure.

# IT Data / Networks Tech, University of New Mexico

Jan 2013 - Dec 2015

Tech in charge of network Ethernet, Server/Switch, and wireless maintenance. Developed tracking, cost basing for wireless setup/management. Updated/Upgraded/Created Programs for Network Diagrams, Spreadsheets, Information/Ticketing management, and web procedures.

# **Education**

### Certificate: Deep Dive Coding Bootcamp

Jul 2018 - Present

CNM Ingenuity, 10-week, 400 hour, mobile-first Full Stack Web Development Coding Bootcamp

#### BS: Psychology / Minor Chemistry

Jan 2013 - Dec 2018

University of New Mexico